all right so now I'm going to try
something different because I've nothing
down for a semester so I'm just going to
talk and see what comes up so random
Apple 30 while at groundswell also
wanted to make a list of ways that can
help social enterprises because I do
acknowledge that a lot of my ideas cause
unemployment for people and that's maybe
not the greatest when we don't have
assist us a social safety net set up
part of what I want to be able to do is
support businesses and cooperatives by
lessening the need for marketing getting
the word out there as to what they do
and what they offer
so I guess idea 30-knot I guess using
language like that is a cooperative
directory so knowing where you can go to
support member-owned and worker owned
businesses I'd like to know so yeah just
a cooperative directory that is Apple 30